POOJA H. PATIL

WEB & MOBILE APPS DEVELOPER

+91 9620434274 | pooja.h.patil90@gmail.com | www.linkedin.com/in/pooja-h-patil | Bangalore, India

ABOUT ME

Im a front-end developer with 5+ years of work experience. I love developing high-performing, scaling and intuitive user interfaces for Mobile and Web applications while continuing to learn and expand my knowledge on cutting-edge technologies.

MY SKILLS

ANGULAR
HTML & CSS

JAVASCRIPT
SASS & SCSS
NODE JS
BOOTSTRAP
TITANIUM & IONIC
UNIT TESTING
SQL

RECOGNITIONS

- Recieved constellation award from Accenture.
- Award recived from Philips for excellent technical skills and phenomenal turn-around time for the feature deliveries.

STRENGTHS

- Effective communication skills,
- Quick learner
- Outstanding problem-solving skills
- Capability of working efficiently under aggressive deadlines

WORK EXPERIENCE

GE - GENERAL ELECTRIC

(Jan 2017 - Present)

- Established strong relationship with TPMs/UX team to understand the customers, business processes via Functional walkthrough sessions and Backlog grooming sessions
- Designed the UI level architecture of the application
- Developed Dynamic loading of the UI components based on different criteria and hence reducing the amount of redundant code
- Made the components customizable for different needs in the application
- Mentored juniors to develop and implement the best practices and ensured adherence to prescribed UX/UI guidelines, consistency in design across the application

PHILIPS (Client location)

(Jan 2016 - Aug 2016)

- Involved in developing a web application using Angular 1.
- Have integrated Solr search into the application.
- Integrated the web application within Sisense a BI tool.

ACCENTURE

+

(Jan 2013 - Jan 2017)

- Actively involved in developing mobile applications with Appcelerator and Ionic frameworks.
- Worked on a chat-bot application with Angular 1 and integrated it with firebase a realtime database.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING

(2008 - 2012)

Visvesvaraya Technological University (VTU)

Studied in Sapthagiri college of engineering under Information science and engineering branch with an aggregate of **76.06%**.

INTERESTS

-









MUSIC

PHOTOGRAPHY

TRAVEL

PIANO